丽芙  准备好《太空狼人》摄影了吗
Liv, you ready for your "space werewolves" photo shoot?
退后  愚蠢的人类  不然就尝尝我愤怒的滋味吧
Stand back, humanoid, or feel my fury.
哇  你看起来帅呆了
Whoa. You look awesome.
谢了  爸爸
Thanks, dad.
我们开始吧
Now let's do this.
咆哮
Snarl.
嚎叫
Growl.
再狂吠
Howl.
让我见识见识你的凶猛
Show me fierce.
砰  啪  咋样
Boom, pow, Wha-cha!
不
No!
爸  他们送来粘盔甲的胶水
Dad, the armor glue they sent me
应该是永久有效的啊
said it's supposed to be permanent.
别担心  趁你衣服没散架之前
Don't worry. I got some fantastic shots
我拍了几张顶好的照片
before your suit fell apart.
哦  太好了  这张真不错
Oh, great. That one's perfect.
现在我可以把痒痒的耳朵摘下来了
Now I can take these itchy ears off.
嗷
Ow.
它们卡住了
They're stuck.
噢 好吧 我的獠牙也卡住了
Oh, okay. So are my fangs.
真是奇怪
That's so weird.
他们送来的化妆胶水
The makeup glue that they sent me
写着说只有20分钟有效
says it's only supposed to last 20 minutes.
而粘盔甲的胶水写的是“永久有效”
And the armor glue says "permanent."